<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HTB on From Bits to Bytes</title>
    <link>https://bhavik-kanejiya.github.io/tags/htb/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HTB on From Bits to Bytes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://bhavik-kanejiya.github.io/tags/htb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HTB TwoMillion Walkthrough</title>
      <link>https://bhavik-kanejiya.github.io/blog/htb-twomillion-walkthrough/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bhavik-kanejiya.github.io/blog/htb-twomillion-walkthrough/</guid>
      <description>Box Info Attribute Details Level Easy OS Linux Box URL HTB-TwoMillion Box Status Retired About Box TwoMillion is an Easy difficulty Linux box that was released to celebrate reaching 2 million users on HackTheBox. The box features an old version of the HackTheBox platform that includes the old hackable invite code. After hacking the invite code an account can be created on the platform. The account can be used to enumerate various API endpoints, one of which can be used to elevate the user to an Administrator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTB Cap Walkthrough</title>
      <link>https://bhavik-kanejiya.github.io/blog/htb-cap-walkthrough/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bhavik-kanejiya.github.io/blog/htb-cap-walkthrough/</guid>
      <description>Box Info Attribute Details Level Easy OS Linux Box URL https://app.hackthebox.com/machines/Cap Box Status Retired About Box Cap is an easy difficulty Linux machine running an HTTP server that performs administrative functions, including performing network captures. Improper controls result in Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR), giving access to another user&amp;rsquo;s capture. The capture contains plaintext credentials and can be used to gain foothold. A Linux capability is then leveraged to escalate to root.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
