<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on From bits to bytes</title>
        <link>https://bhavik-kanejiya.github.io/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on From bits to bytes</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://bhavik-kanejiya.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>Let’s do a peek inside the admin dashboard - Abuse API endpoint</title>
            <link>https://bhavik-kanejiya.github.io/posts/2022/01/lets-do-a-peek-inside-the-admin-dashboard-abuse-api-endpoint/</link>
            <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://bhavik-kanejiya.github.io/posts/2022/01/lets-do-a-peek-inside-the-admin-dashboard-abuse-api-endpoint/</guid>
            <description>There is broken access control in the API which helps an employee to become the admin of a workspace but with limited permissions.
Application introduction It’s a productivity app that has over 2 million+ users and is used by business to track employee project time and expenses.
Key Features There are many features, but these are some of the most important ones:
User can join multiple workspaces User can create their own workspace The admin of a workspace can invite other user by email How does the application work?</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>There is broken access control in the API which helps an employee to become the admin of a workspace but with limited permissions.</p>
<p><img alt="Desktop View" src="/images/api-blog/Header.jpg"></p>
<h2 id="application-introduction">Application introduction</h2>
<p>It’s a productivity app that has over 2 million+ users and is used by business to track employee project time and expenses.</p>
<h2 id="key-features">Key Features</h2>
<p>There are many features, but these are some of the most important ones:</p>
<ul>
<li>User can join multiple workspaces</li>
<li>User can create their own workspace</li>
<li>The admin of a workspace can invite other user by email</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="how-does-the-application-work">How does the application work?</h2>
<p>A user can join multiple workspaces from one account, but the user ID will be the same across all the workspace. So, the user create personal workspace and along with company&rsquo;s workspace</p>
<p>The API uses the workspace ID to interact with the application.</p>
<p><em>This is what the request look a like</em>:
<img alt="Desktop View" src="/images/api-blog/Request.png"></p>
<p><em>This is how Workspace ID look a like</em>:
<img alt="Desktop View" src="/images/api-blog/Table.png"></p>
<p>While the test for role-based broken access control, uses multi-account containers where cookies are separated by container, allowing us to use the web with multiple accounts.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>While the test for role-based broken access control, Use <a href="https://github.com/yeswehack/PwnFox">PwnFox</a> to colorize the tab and burpsuite proxy history.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>There are a few sections that are only visible to the admin. On the user side, we have limited functionalities. If we change the workspace ID directly, it will redirect me to its homepage. We use burp’s match and replace feature to replace the Workspace ID.</p>
<p>This is the final result when the user successfully matches and replaces the personal workspace ID with the company’s workspace ID.</p>
<p><img alt="Window shadow" src="/images/api-blog/comp.png"></p>
<h2 id="step-to-reproduce">Step to Reproduce</h2>
<p><img alt="Desktop View" src="/images/api-blog/Steps.png"></p>
<h2 id="end-note">End Note</h2>
<p>If you have enjoyed this article, Share this with your friends. Thank you!
<a href="https://linktr.ee/bhavikkanejiya">https://linktr.ee/bhavikkanejiya</a></p>
<h2 id="references">References:</h2>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mpw1Lo3GAK0">Automating IDORs with Autorize - Common API Bugs Pt. 2 - IDORs &amp; Access Control Issues</a> by <a href="https://aseemshrey.in/">@Asseem_shrey</a></li>
<li><a href="https://blog.yeswehack.com/yeswerhackers/pimpmyburp-pwnfox-autorize-find-idor/">PimpMyBurp #1 – PwnFox + Autorize</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3K1-a7dnA60">Burp Suite tutorial: IDOR vulnerability automation using Autorize and AutoRepeater</a></li>
<li><a href="https://blog.usamav.dev/two-account-takeover-bugs-worth-4300-dollar-bounty">Two account takeover bugs worth $$$$</a></li>
</ul>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
